no bro
old guy
recording in the rain is very complicated
how to attract customer
with gas station
and then galley
today is the 75th
he hand
cookie for us
is on
congratulations
brought 1 little gift for you here
you deserve
I don't know if you'll like it
all you need is
learn to tell stories
I was talking about you
arrive there
every morning
I wake up and have my coffee here with Juninho from the gas station
here at the high post Anchieta has no client
have friends
can
return
there
can give that laugh
give a laugh
and there bro
can leave Juninho
and here they do the fuel test
in front of customers
and
in case your car is dirty
here is a powder vacuum cleaner
free for those who want to give 1 deal
and here they have the best cheese bread
stuffed you can imagine
products or services are not sold alone
and if you want
learn how to create your own storytellin
in order to attract brands
people
companies or services without killing their authenticity
I created 1 workshop called beatbox
I will make 1 face-to-face meeting
only for 60 people here in the high post Anchieta
on top of that shed Ali oh
but due to space
places are limited
and if you are interested
send 1 DM to me
writing
hmm wat zie ik ervan
valeu tamo together
then I think of something there caraca
it's on fire today